First of all, congratulations. I want to
get the proper pronunciation of your
name, though, so let me hear it. Uh
>> Dylan Daman.
>> Okay. So, we're we're right on that
because people have gone in different
variations. Um did you have a nickname
growing up or do you have one now?
>> I've gone through a few. Right now, it's
just been DT.
>> DT. All right. All right. What was going
through your mind? Top 25 pick in the
2026 draft.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I mean I was really just
sitting there just just happy to be
there at the draft to start to be there
with my family and and other people that
really supported me was amazing.
Eventually we go through the draft and
it gets to the Bears pick and I like
turned away. So I turn my my head to the
right and Jake starts calling my name.
My brother was sitting right next to me.
He's like, "Dyl, don't do it." I look
down, the phone's ringing and then I
called up like, "Hey, this is the
Chicago Bears." And I talked to like 10
different people and then I was just
like extremely thank to be picked by
them.
>> I'm obsessed with safety since I was a
little kid. I love safeties. I think
it's,
you know, tone setter, playmaker, and
you seem to check all those boxes. But
I'm going to let you tell Bears fans,
what type of player are you?
>> I'm a kind of player that just all he
thinks about is football. Like, growing
up, ever since I was four, has always
been football. No doubt in my mind
there. I love everything about it.
Lifting, watching film, training, being
aggressive, being violent. Like, it's a
violent physical game. So, you got to be
like calm a little bit, but when you get
on the field, you flip that switch.
>> All right. All right, I got to ask you
about something that's been circulating.
Apparently, your mother sent a photo.
The family all in Brian Erlacer
uniforms. The genesis of this. Were you
guys Bears fans? I mean, what's the
story?
>> When I was young, we were in Northern
Indiana until I was four and then we
moved to Indianapolis. But while we were
in Northern Indiana, we were Bears fans.
I was pretty young, so I didn't remember
much from then. But I heard in the photo
they had to photoshop me in cuz I I
wasn't staying still when I was a little
kid.
You're still not staying still.
>> Yeah, I know.
>> You're a marauder back there running
around uh with your hair on fire. Uh
that's a pretty cool story. So, what
comes around goes around. So, now you
guys are back in business here with the
Bears. Congratulations, man.
>> Thank you.